I had my bangs cut!
Now it's just below my eyebrows.
It looks good. My eyesight has improved by one. I'll work on it.
What's your hair style today?
Oh my God, we're being filmed.
I'm going to edit it.
Oh, crush.
Oh, here it comes.
It's curly.
Yes, I'm breaking it now, and the manager fixed it, and I'd like to put it on.
What do you think? Is it weird? I'd like to put it on like this.
What do you think? Is it weird?
Is it weird?
I'm smiling, so I think it's a good sign. Please go ahead.
I'm the girl you've heard so much about.
I want you to say that you're the girl I like. I'm trying so hard.
No?
I'm not?
No, I'm not.
Me?
No, you're not.
No. - No?
Is that right?
That's number one.
This is number 2.
Number 2.
This is the last three times.
I'm number 2.
Then, I'm number 1.
You're number 1, right?
Yes, I'll sing. I'll sing. Then, you're number one. I'll unleash it on the world.
I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it, I like it.
I'm not alone.
Shoo-shoo!
Laughs.
What's your name?
Hmm?
What?
I'm curious.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but thank you for your time. When I asked you for advice about my love life.
I realized I was in love.
You know what I'm talking about.
No... which one of us is in love?
No. 4, which one of us is in love with a boy?
I'm just spinning on my feet
None of them understood.
I guess you're right. I guess it's a mistake.
I'll tell you what.
Spring's first. We're going to start the show.
I'll let the wind blow, but my, my, my.
A single flower. I want her.
In the space, in the words, in the heat of the pine trees...
Even if this summer has come, there's no doubt in my mind that it's just a little bit...
Dreams, petals, sky, river, moon, color
The world seems splendid
What can I say then?
Men are like that.
I don't know.
I like it. I like it.
I like nothing else.
I don't know how to say it.
I want him.
Much more personality tension
Violence Friendship vs. Contribution
The story of the chosen hero
Everyone wanted to believe
Rarity's Princtor
From the Hunchy Fans.
Choose Love Learn Party
Tokyo I can study
Up, up, up, up, up
I'll always be the hero.
I love you all!
Let's laugh at beads in the daytime
I've got a little something going on.
Yeah, I know.
Sometimes I take a break, and it's less firewood.An occasional break would reduce that too.
It only makes sense.
Because today...
You're the one who sweated that much.
That's a gift. Or it's growth.
Either one is great either way.
Good job, Sensual.
Always, always, today, a sensation inside
me
meme
me me
meme me me, I'll never forget the moment when our dreams overlap
Let's laugh through our tears
The magic I've been conveying since birth
one step forward one small step forward
to a meaningless life
no matter what, even today
You've worked so hard to be here
Is that the end or is it just for you
Tomorrow and the day after tomorrow, you'll still be amazing
Good job, Kel.
Much more evolving sensation
Tomorrow, too, I'm sure
You can do it, guys.
Viva la viva! ♪ Pounding, pounding, pounding ♪
Let's see how it flutters
The pain of the sparkling sun is beating down
We're only looking at each other for a moment
It's only for a moment
Eternity's plan
Imagination
In all seriousness
Bursting into life
In a spark
Laughing and welcoming each other
The finale is now rust passion mira mira mira shining laughing together welcoming the sun lined up bye bye
Come on, let's go where you're going, lalilari, shining shooting star
Make a wish for me
Love Parade
Tales that pass by
Love Balade
Oh, beautiful life now
Love, let the time be now
Tomorrow will be now, let it be then